Search

    * Bahasa IndonesiaDeutschEnglishEspañolFrançaisHungarianItalianoNederlandsPolskiPortuguês (Brasil)RomânăSuomiSvenskaTürkçeΕλληνικάБългарскиРусскийСрпскиУкраїнськаالعربيةفارسی日本語한국어

Privacy Policy
==============

The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated when you use our site. Personal information includes your name, e-mail addresses, click-through activity and any other personal information you may provide here.  
  
**Email and other private information**  
  
When you decide to go through registration process in order to obtain personal user account at LyricsTranslate.com, you are proposed to fill registration form which asks for your email and name. Your email is needed for us to complete registration process and to restore your account password if you will ask about it. We will not send you any further spam-information messages. Actually, you will get emails from LyricsTranslate only if you chose to - it can be used to notify you about private messages, sent to you by other users, or satisfaction of your request or appearance of new comments to your articles etc.  
  
Later on you log in to your personal user profile page, where you see questions about your age, gender, spoken languages, location, occupation, interests and alternative contact information (your Yahoo, Google, Skype, MSN, ICQ accounts). This information will be displayed to other people - so if you don't want to be contacted or don't want to disclose any of your private information, just leave any or all of these fields blank, they are not obligatory to fill.  
  
Please, do not use your email address as your user-name unless you are fully aware of fact that it will become visible to all visitors of the site.  
  
**How do I delete my account?**  
  
To delete your account, go to your profile page, click "Edit" and then "Cancel account" button. Please keep in mind that this action is irreversible.  
  
**How do I delete my personal data?**  
  
To delete your personal data, you can delete your account (instructions are above), or contact site administration: [Contact Us](https://lyricstranslate.com/en/contact)  
  
**Traffic data**  
  
Each time a visitor comes to a LyricsTranslate.com Web site, our server logs some basic technical information such as browser and platform, visitor's domain name and referral data. We are also processing the visitor's activity through our site. We may present the results of this processing to outside companies, but no one will be able to identify you or contact you because of this data.  
  
**Cookies**  
  
Lyricstranslate uses cookies and other technologies (such as web beacons and advertising identifiers) in order to differentiate you from other users and keep developing our Services. [read more](https://lyricstranslate.com/en/cookies-policy)  
  
[Your cookie storage preferences for lyricstranslate.com](javascript:void(document.querySelector('#ot-sdk-btn-floating%20button.ot-floating-button__open').click());)  
  
**Ads**  
  
We use a third-party to provide monetization technologies for our site. You can review their privacy and cookie policy here:

**Other sites**  
  
LyricsTranslate.com may contain many links to other sites on the Web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other Web sites.  
  
**Thanks for using LyricsTranslate.com! Your feedback is welcome.**

Russia is waging a disgraceful war on Ukraine.     Stand With Ukraine!

[How you can support Ukraine](https://war.ukraine.ua/support-ukraine/) 🇺🇦 ❤️

Site activity

New request

[Ded Archimed - Сплотиться вокруг президента (Splotitʹsya vokrug prezidenta)](https://lyricstranslate.com/en/request/%D1%81%D0%BF%D0%BB%D0%BE%D1%82%D0%B8%D1%82%D1%8C%D1%81%D1%8F-%D0%B2%D0%BE%D0%BA%D1%80%D1%83%D0%B3-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%B7%D0%B8%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BD%D1%82%D0%B0)

Russian → English

New translation

Finnish → French

New collection

New request

Russian → Serbian

New translation

[Georg Friedrich Händel - HWV 58 Semele, III, 56: "O Ecstasy Of Happiness.](https://lyricstranslate.com/en/georg-friedrich-hand-hwv-58-semele-iii-56-neapolitan)

English → Neapolitan

New translation

Spanish → English

New comment

Ну да, стрела Амура пронзила сердце насквозь и ...  [more](https://lyricstranslate.com/en/comment/1148136#comment-1148136)

New translation

Korean → Ukrainian

New comment

Μην έχεις τύψεις, ξέρω delivery που βγάζουν πάνω ...  [more](https://lyricstranslate.com/en/comment/1148135#comment-1148135)

New song

Japanese

[LyricsTranslate.com](https://lyricstranslate.com/) – the world's largest repository of lyrics translations

[Join us!](https://lyricstranslate.com/en/user/register?destination=how-request-translation) It's free, you can add and request translations, and see no ads.

© 2008-2024 LyricsTranslate.com

Interface language

Bahasa IndonesiaDeutschEnglishEspañolFrançaisHungarianItalianoNederlandsPolskiPortuguês (Brasil)RomânăSuomiSvenskaTürkçeΕλληνικάБългарскиРусскийСрпскиУкраїнськаالعربيةفارسی日本語한국어

Theme

DarkLight

Artists:

Do not share my Personal Information.
